

Applicant for:

Senior/Middle Java Engineer ~2,000\$

Dr.JOY 30 September 2021

Ngoc

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Ngoc skipped the cover letter.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name NGUYEN THI NGOC

Nationality Vietnamese

Date of Birth December, 8th 1989 Phone No. (84) 983 793 003

Email nguyenngocktt2@gmail.com



EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

2007 – 2011 B.S of Mathematics and Informatics Da Nang University of Education, Vietnam

CERTIFICATE AND AWARD

2012 – 2013 CNAM2008 Network Administrator PNH, Ha Noi 2013 – 2015 Higher Diploma in Software Engineering FPT-APTECH, Ha Noi Vietnam

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Have five years of work experience in web application development that includes two years in web application development with Ruby and three years in web application development with Java (There are more than one year's working with Java Enterprise technologies).

I've worked with both Window and Ubuntu Operating System.

I've worked with many frameworks such as Bootstrap, Jquery, AngularJS, ReactJS, Ruby on Rails, Hibernate, Struts2, Spring, JSF.

In that environments, I'm able to code in many languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, Ruby, Java

I'm used to using Sublime IDE for ruby projects and Eclipse IDE for java projects.

About view technical, I'm able to use JSON, JSP, Facelets, Primefaces.

Source-codes of the projects is manged by SNV, GIT.

Almost Java projects use Maven, which is a project management tool.

The projects are written in Ruby use a Nginx, enterprise application project uses a Widfly and web java application projects use a Apache Tomcat, as a web server.

I performed role as a back-end developer,

Cooperative and able to perform within a team-oriented atmosphere.

Good level of understanding in English that includes reading and writing technical specifications/documents.

I worked as Ruby Developer at Framgia VietNam company from 2015 to 2017.

I worked as Java Developer at FPT Software from 2017 to 2018.

I worked as Java Developer at Synergix VietNam from 2019 to present.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015/6 ~ 2015/12: Ruby developer in mobile application project (Cosplay No.1)

Responsibilities: Coding and Rspec testing, Fix bugs.

Technologies: Os (Ubuntu),

- -- Testing (Rspec),
- -- Development tools (Sublime, Git),
- -- Framework (Ruby on Rails, Jquery, Bootstrap),
- -- Database(MySQL)
- -- Programming language (Ruby)

2016/1 ~ 2016/7: Ruby developer in web application project (Restaurant Management)

Responsibilities: Analyze the requirements, Coding and Rspec testing, Research services(google, amazon) Technologies: Os (Ubuntu),

- -- Testing (Rspec),
- -- Development tools (Sublime, Git),
- -- Framework (Ruby on Rails, Jquery, Bootstrap, AngularJS),
- Services (Google cloud storage, Google BigQuery, SendGrid, Amazon S3, Slack api),
- -- Database(MySQL)
- -- Programming language (Ruby, Javascript, HTML, CSS)

$2016/8 \sim 2017/3$: Ruby developer in web application project (Create a website or build a blog, mail template)

Responsibilities: Coding and Rspec testing, Fix bugs

Technologies: Os(Ubuntu),

- -- Development tools(Sublime, git),
- -- Testing(rspec),
- -- Services(amazon S3),
- -- Framework(Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, ReactJS, Jquery, Bootstrap),
- -- Database(MongoDB)
- -- Programming language(Ruby, Javascript, HTML, CSS)

2017/6 ~ 2017/7: Java developer in web application project (Sales Management)

Responsibilities: Coding and analyzing the requirements.

Technologies: Os(Window)

- -- IDE(Eclipse) ,
- -- Development tools(SVN, UML),
- -- Web server(Apache Tomcat),
- -- View technical(JSP, JSON),
- -- Framework(Struts 2, Jquery, Bootstrap),
- -- Programming language(Java, SQL, Javascript, HTML, CSS)

2017/8 ~ 2017/10: Java developer in web application project (Athlete Relationship Management)

Responsibilities: Coding and Testing

Technologies: Os(Window)

- -- IDE(Eclipse),
- -- Development tools(SVN, Git),
- -- Framework(Intarfrm, Jquery, Bootstrap),
- -- Database(PostgreSQL),
- -- Programming language(Java, SQL, Javascript, HTML, CSS)

2017/11 ~ 2018/3: Java developer in microservices application project (Domain Management)

Responsibilities: Coding and Testing

Technologies: Os(Ubuntu)

- -- IDE(Intellij),
- -- Development tools(Git),
- Framework(Spring Rest, Spring Boot, Spring JPA, Spring Jdbc),
- -- Project management tools(Gradle, Docker),
- -- Api Gateway(Kong),
- -- Database(PostgreSQL, Redis),
- -- Programming Language(Java, SQL)

2018/4 \sim 2018/5: (personal project) web application

Technologies: Ubuntu, Intellij, Git, Java(Spring MVC, Spring Boot, Spring JPA, Spring Jdpc), Maven,

Thymeleaf, HTML, CSS, Jquery, heroku, apache tomcat. Git: https://github.com/ngocnquyenctt/spring-web-app

Heroku: https://sale-management-app.herokuapp.com/salesOrder?lang=en

2018/6 ~ 2018/10: Java developer in web application project (Database, reports, form, records management process)

Responsibilities: Coding, fix bugs

Technologies: Os(Window)

- -- IDE(Eclipse),
- -- Development tools(Git),
- -- Project Management Tools(Maven),
- -- Web server(nginx),
- -- RabbitMQ,
- -- Framework(Spring),
- -- Database(MongoDB, Redis),
- -- Programming language(Java)

2018/12 ~ 2019/3: Java developer in salesforce application project (Examination and treatment system)

Responsibilities: Coding, Research salesforce

Technologies: Os(Window),

- -- Apex,
- -- SOSQL,
- -- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

2019/7 ~ present: Java developer in java enterprise application project (ERP System)

Responsibilities: research system (business), coding and testing, fix bugs.

Technologies: Os(Window),

- -- IDE(Eclipse),
- -- Development tools(SVN),
- -- Project Management Tools(Maven),
- -- Web server(WildFly),
- -- JPA
- -- Framework(JSF),
- -- View technicals(Facelets, Primefaces),
- -- Database(PostgreSQL, DB2),
- -- Programming language(Java)

SKILLS

Communication, Self-management, Willingness to learn, Thinking skills, Resilience Special skill: Resilience, Thinking skills

PERSONAL QUALITIES

Eager to learn,
Sense of responsibility,
Passion & creative & curious,
Carefulness in all the works done are my greatest strengths

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Reading books E-commerce / community development services

ASPIRATIONS

Worked in professional environment, Professional development opportunities and attractive salary, Time: full time, Place of work: Ha noi Viet nam

Nguyen Thi Ngoc's CV - Confidential